coachingactuaries.com 2016-04-07

# Privacy Policy - Coaching Actuaries

### Privacy Statement

Coaching Actuaries is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Coaching Actuaries Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Coaching Actuaries website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

### Collection of your Personal Information

Coaching Actuaries collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address and telephone number. Coaching Actuaries also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. 

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Coaching Actuaries. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Coaching Actuaries for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Coaching Actuaries Web site. 

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Coaching Actuaries public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Coaching Actuaries does not read any of your private online communications. 

Coaching Actuaries encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Coaching Actuaries so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Coaching Actuaries is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Coaching Actuaries and Coaching Actuaries family of Web sites. 

### Use of your Personal information

Coaching Actuaries collects and uses your personal information to operate the Coaching Actuaries Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Coaching Actuaries also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Coaching Actuaries and its affiliates. Coaching Actuaries may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. 

Coaching Actuaries does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Coaching Actuaries may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Coaching Actuaries may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Coaching Actuaries, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

Coaching Actuaries does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent. 

Coaching Actuaries keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Coaching Actuaries, in order to determine what Coaching Actuaries services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Coaching Actuaries to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. 

Coaching Actuaries Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Coaching Actuaries or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Coaching Actuaries; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Coaching Actuaries, or the public. 

### Use of Cookies

The Coaching Actuaries Web site uses "cookies" to personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file saved to your hard disk by a Web server. 

Cookies are a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to inform the Web server that you returned to a specific page. For example, when you register with Coaching Actuaries, a cookie helps Coaching Actuaries recall your specific information. When you return to the same Coaching Actuaries Web page, the information you previously provided can be retrieved. In short, cookies allow you to customize your Coaching Actuaries features. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies. Usually you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you will not be able to login or use the interactive features of the Coaching Actuaries' free or paid services. 

### Security of your Personal information

Coaching Actuaries secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Coaching Actuaries secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. 

### Changes to this Statement

Coaching Actuaries will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Coaching Actuaries encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Coaching Actuaries is protecting your information. 

### Contact Information

Coaching Actuaries welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Coaching Actuaries has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Coaching Actuaries at [support@coachingactuaries.com](mailto:support@coachingactuaries.com) or visit us at https://www.coachingactuaries.com/Help. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
